Guide to the J. Wilson Morrow Papers, 1930-1968 and undated RL.11010
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Wilson Morrow papers
1930-1968 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
Morrow, J. Wilson
RL.11010
0.4 Linear Feet
Businessman who sold household appliances and radios in Wernersville, Pa., during the 1930s-1940s. Collection spans 1930-1968 and includes memos, service and repair bulletins, newsletters, sales and product manuals, price and product lists, blueprints and photographs. Companies represented include Edison Electric, General Electric, Hotpoint, Maytag, Metropolitan Edison, Raymond Rosen, Stromberg-Carlson, Sylvania and Westinghouse. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Collection Overview
Collection spans 1930-1968 and includes memos, service and repair bulletins, newsletters, sales and product manuals, price and product lists, blueprints and photographs. Companies represented include Edison Electric, General Electric, Hotpoint, Maytag, Metropolitan Edison, Raymond Rosen, Stromberg-Carlson, Sylvania and Westinghouse. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48-hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Arrangement
Organized alphabetically.
Provenance
The J. Wilson Morrow Papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2004.
Related Materials
Related materials may be found in the following Hartman Center collections:
Jim Brown Papers
Foote, Cone & Belding Communications, Inc. Records
J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm Microfilm Investigations
J. Walter Thompson Company. Marketing Vertical File
Stanley C. Marshall Papers.
Nicole Di Bona Peterson Collection of Advertising Cookbooks
Household appliances; Pennsylvania -- Commerce; Household appliances, Electric; Household appliances -- United States; Household appliances industry; Household appliances, Electric -- United States; Household appliances -- Maintenance and repair; Household appliances industry -- United States; Sales executives; Household appliances -- Maintenance and repair -- United States; Sales executives -- United States; Pennsylvania; Sylvania Electric Products, Inc.; Westinghouse Electric Corporation; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History; General Electric Company; Maytag Company; Metropolitan Edison Company; Stromberg-Carlson telephone manufacturing co.; Edison Electric Appliance Co.; Morrow, J. Wilson
- American Greeting Publishers--Stock control cards, 1943 (Box 1)
- Bob White Frosted Foods (Frosty Acres brand)--Price list, 1968 (Box 1)
- Central Sink Cabinets--Specifications and photographs, undated (Box 1)
- Easy Washing Machine Co.--Service bulletins, 1936 and undated (Box 1)
- Edison/Hotpoint--Commercial Cooking Manual Vol.II: Sales Presentations, undated (Box 1)
- General Electric--Disctric circulars, 1937-1938 (Box 1)
- General Electric--Salesman's Bulletin, 1937 and undated (Box 1)
- General Electric--Service Bulletin, 1937-1938 (Box 1)
- General Electric--Service bulletins, 1937-1942 (Box 1)
- Keystone Appliances--Product bulletins, 1935-1936 (Box 1)
- Maytag--Parts/price lists, 1933-1940 (Box 1)
- Maytag--Service manuals and miscellaneous, 1941-1947 and undated (Box 1)
- Metropolitan Edison--Specifications data, 1941 (Box 1)
- Notes and miscellaneous, 1930-1939 and undated (Box 1)
- Raymond Rosen Co.--Radio Bulletin, 1935-1938 (Box 1)
- Stromberg-Carlson--Solder Nuggets; Wartime Radio Service, 1937-1942 (Box 1)
- Successful Servicing (publication), 1935 (Box 1)
- Sylvania--Sylvania News, 1937 (Box 1)
- Westinghouse--Service Beacon, 1944 (Box 1)
- Westinghouse--Service bulletins, 1939-1941 (Box 1)